

Sagar Vijay Warang

Programmer Analyst

Skilled software engineer with nearly 2 years of experience and certified Salesforce professional. I have a methodical, customer-focused approach to work and a strong drive to see things through completion. I am a fast learner who adapts quickly to change, and I am keen to learn new technologies.

warang.sagar3@gmail.com

Solapur, Maharashtra, India

(iii) 03 September 1996

Work Experience

Programmer Analyst - Salesforce Developer Cognizant

03/2021 - Present

Pune, India

Achievement/Task:

- Client Project Bayer (ANZ).
- Unit Test for Apex Classes and debugging.
- Created Triggers, Batch Apex, and LWC component.
- Created custom Object, fields, rules, Custom metadata Based on requirements.
- Created flows, Process Builder, Email alerts.
- Project follows the Agile –Scrum framework, monitor Using Jira tool.

Training Project

Cognizant

03/2021 -04/2021

Pune, India

Achievement/Task:

- Product booking website using Experience cloud.
- Built Auto spare sell App on sandbox for admin.
- Email alert after booking appointment.
- Created User, roles, Page layout, OWD settings.
- Built LWC search component.

College Project

Experimental Investigation of Magnetic Fuel Conditioner

September 2019 - March 2020 Solapur, India

Achievement/Task:

- Establish correct fuel burning parameter.
- Complete fuel Burning & maximum energy.
- Lowest possible level of Toxic emission.
- Data visualization and Data analytics.

Diploma Project

Pedal Operated Power Generator.

November 2016 - March 2017

Solapur, India

Achievement/Task:

- Mechanical work converts into Electric.
- Implemented Gears mechanism & DC Generator.
- Used for changing small devices.

EDUCATION

B.E - Mechanical (8.32 CGPA)

NBN Sinhgad , Solapur

2017 - 2020

Diploma - Mechanical (66.47 %)

Government Polytechnic, Solapur 2014-2017

Skills

- Domain: Salesforce-Customization & Configuration.
- Professional Skills: Approval processes, Validation rules, Data loader, Reports and dashboards, Apex Triggers and controller, Data Management, Data Modelling, Collection, Process Automation, SOSL, SOQL, LWC.
- Programming Languages: C, Java, Apex, HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript.
- Platform: VS Code, Force.com.
- Database: MySQL, SOQL, SOSL.

Certification

Salesforce Certified Administrator.
Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I.

Other Achievement

- Completed value addition program of Catia V5 Held by college with A+ Grade.
- Appreciation from office of the Superintendent Police, Solapur. For Online E-Service Book Employment data management system.

Co-Curricular Activities

- Completed Journey2Salesforce program.
- Completed 5x Super badges and Ranger rank in Trailhead.
- Trained 2 Students on Salesforce Basic.
- Promotional Head of National level Tech Fest (2018-19).
- Swatch Bharat Summer Internship (2018-19).

SOFT SKILLS

Decision Making Self-Motivated
Problem-solving attitude Quick Learner
Effective Communicator

in linkedin.com/in/sagar-warang-5903b8228/

🕏 trailblazer.me/id/sagarwarang

919689311853